Records of the Council on Hemispheric Affairs, 1975-2002 M1354
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Materials related to Brazil and Canada (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 134)
- Materials related to Brazil, continued (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 135)
- Materials related to Brazil and Guatemala (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 136)
- Materials related to Brazil, Canada, and Guatemala; the subject file "Foreign Affairs" (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 137)
- Materials related to Brazil, Guatemala, and Grenada (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 138)
- Materials related to Brazil, Cuba, and Guatemala (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 139)
- Materials related to Brazil and Guatemala; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 140)
- Materials related to Brazil and Guatemala, 1980s (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 141)
- Materials related to Brazil, Panama, and Paraguay (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 142)
- Materials related to Panama, Paraguay, and O.A.S. [Organization of American States]; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 143)
- Materials related to Panama, Paraguay, Barbados, and O.A.S. [Organization of American States]; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 144)
- Materials related to Honduras, Paraguay, Costa Rica, Puerto Rico, and O.A.S. [Organization of American States]; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 145)
- Materials related to Panama and Paraguay; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 146)
- Materials related to Venezuela, Cuba, El Salvador, Guyana, Trinidad; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 147)
- Materials related to Taiwan, Switzerland, Soviet Union, Nicaragua, Mexico, Central America; subject files ("Drugs of Abuse," "World Freedom Council," etc.); personal files; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 148)
- Materials related to Israel, Japan, Honduras; subject files; personal files (mostly letters U, W, K, H, J); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 149)
- Materials related to Iran; subject files ("International Youth Year," "Southern Air Transport," etc.); personal files (mostly letters K, H); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 150)
- Personal files (letters G, S, M-N). (Box 151)
- Personal files (letters J, K, M, N, S, R). (Box 152)
- Personal files (the letter M); materials related to Simpson-Mazzoli Bill; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 153)
- Personal files (letters R, S); subject files. (Box 154)
- Personal files (letters R, S); subject files. (Box 155)
- Materials related to Panama; subject files ("Right Wing," etc.); personal files (the letter R); miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 156)
- Materials related to Panama (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 157)
- Materials related to Panama, continued (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 158)
- Materials related to Panama and Guyana; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 159)
- Materials related to Guyana (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 160)
- Photocopies of miscellaneous documents related to Cuba, Grenada, Vietnam, etc. (including Grenada - State Department documents). (Box 161)
- Materials related to Guyana; miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 162)
- Miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 163)
- Materials related to Guatemala; miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 164)
- Materials related to Guatemala, continued (clippings, leaflets, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); miscellaneous publications. (Box 165)
- Materials related to Grenada (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); miscellaneous publications. (Box 166)
- Materials related to Grenada, continued (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 167)
- Materials related to Grenada and Nicaragua (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 168)
- Materials related to Nicaragua and Peru (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 169)
- Materials related to Nicaragua, continued (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 170)
- Materials related to Nicaragua, continued (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 171)
- Materials related to Dominican Republic, Panama, Honduras, Cuba, Guyana, Mexico, Peru; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 172)
- Materials related to Peru, Grenada, Martinique, Japan; miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 173)
- Materials related to Peru; miscellaneous subject files and personal files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 174)
- Materials related to Cuba, Mexico, Bolivia, Canada, Japan, Panama, Uruguay, Peru; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 175)
- Materials related to Argentina, Mexico, Guatemala, Columbia, Panama; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 176)
- "Elian Case" materials; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 177)
- "Elian Case" materials, continued; materials related to Canada, Haiti, Argentina; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 178)
- Miscellaneous publications (Box 179)
- Materials related to Canada; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 180)
- Materials related to Brazil, Chile, Argentina, Belize, Bolivia; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 181)
- Materials related to Chile, Haiti, Columbia, Ecuador, El Salvador, Guatemala; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 182)
- Miscellaneous clippings and publications, etc. (Box 183)
- Typescripts, clippings, newsletters, brochures, handwritten notes and block notes, miscellaneous. (Box 184)
- Miscellaneous subject and personal files ("Steel," "Tobacco," Treaty of Tlatelolco," etc.). (Box 185)
- Miscellaneous subject and personal files ("Socialist Workers Party," "State Department," etc.). (Box 186)
- Materials related to "Socialist International"; subject and personal files, some arranged alphabetically (A-B). (Box 187)
- Subject and personal files, some arranged alphabetically (A-B); materials related to the topic of immigration. (Box 188)
- Materials related to the topic of immigration and to the International Monetary Fund (IMF). (Box 189)
- Materials related to the topic of immigration and to the International Monetary Fund (IMF), continued; "Brecha" newsletters. (Box 190)
- Newsletters, newspapers, releases. (Box 191)
- Materials related to the Columbus 500 Years Anniversary, other subject files (newsletters, publications, clippings, photocopies, etc.). (Box 192)
- Miscellaneous subject files (newsletters, publications, clippings, photocopies, etc.). (Box 193)
- Miscellaneous subject files, continued (newsletters, publications, clippings, photocopies, etc.). (Box 194)
- Materials related to Brazil; miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 195)
- Materials related to Brazil, Canada, Dominican Republic; miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 196)
- Materials related to Cuba, Columbia, Venezuela; miscellaneous subject files ("Immigration," etc.). (Box 197)
- Materials related to Cuba and Guatemala (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 198)
- Materials related to Cuba, India, El Salvador (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 199)
- Materials related to Cuba, Cuba-Africa and Cuba-Angola relations (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 200)
- Materials related to Cuba, Costa-Rica, and Guatemala (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 201)
- Materials related to Guatemala and El Salvador; miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 202)
- Materials related to El Salvador; miscellaneous subject and personal files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 203)
- Materials related to El Salvador ("Human Rights," "Opposition"), Caribbean / Latin American region, Canada; miscellaneous subject and personal files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 204)
- Materials related to Caribbean; subject and personal ("Duarte") files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 205)
- Materials related to Honduras and El Salvador (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 206)
- Materials related to Honduras and El Salvador, continued (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 207)
- Materials related to Honduras; miscellaneous subject ("Carter Administration") and personal files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 208)
- Materials related to Uruguay and South Africa; materials related to Caribbean Basin Initiative - CBI (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 209)
- Materials related to Spain, Cuba, Sweden, Soviet Union - U.S. relationships, Israel; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 210)
- Materials related to Honduras (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 211)
- Materials related to Honduras, Austria, France, Germany, Hong Kong, Indonesia, Japan, Chile, Guatemala, Columbia, Mexico (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 212)
- Materials related to Mexico, Venezuela, Cuba, Chile, Afganistan, Angola, Africa, Australia, Asia, Uruguay, Honduras, Iran, Portugal (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); miscellaneous materials. (Box 213)
- Materials related to Philippines, Israel, Honduras, Cuba (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); subject files. (Box 214)
- Materials related to Honduras, Nicaragua, Guatemala (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 215)
- Materials related to Nicaragua, Guatemala, Costa Rica, Mexico (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 216)
- Materials related to Guatemala (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 217)
- Materials related to Guatemala (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); subject files arranged alphabetically: Ac-Ag. (Box 218)
- Subject files arranged alphabetically: Ag, continued - Ar (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 219)
- Subject files arranged alphabetically: Ab-Ag, Al-Aq; miscellaneous files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 220)
- Financial documents (receipts, statements, taxes, expenses, telephone bills, reports, handwritten notes, miscellaneous), mostly 1994-1996. (Box 221)
- Financial documents, continued (receipts, statements, taxes, expenses, telephone bills, reports, handwritten notes, miscellaneous), mostly 1994-1996; miscellaneous subject files; miscellaneous publications, some related to Brazil; materials related to Iberian Peninsula. (Box 222)
- Newsletters, bulletins, newspapers, etc. related to Nicaragua and Latin America; subject files related to Hispanic issues in the U.S. (Box 223)
- Newsletters, etc. related to El Salvador; materials related to Iran (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); subject files ("Europe / Latin America, 1990," "Human Rights, General," etc.). (Box 224)
- Subject files ("Gulf Crisis / War," "Free Trade," etc.). (Box 225)
- Materials related to Iran ("Iran - Contra" files); miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 226)
- Materials related to Honduras, Iran (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); subject files ("Immigration," etc.). (Box 227)
- Subject files regarding mostly immigration issues (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 228)
- Miscellaneous publications (bulletins, newsletters, etc.), some related to Guatemala. (Box 229)
- Miscellaneous publications (bulletins, newsletters, etc.), some related to Guatemala (continued). (Box 230)
- Miscellaneous publications (magazines, bulletins, newsletters, etc.), some related to Guatemala (continued). (Box 231)
- Miscellaneous magazines. (Box 232)
- Miscellaneous bulletins, some related to Guatemala and El Salvador. (Box 233)
- Miscellaneous bulletins, some related to Guatemala, El Salvador, Nicaragua; miscellaneous publications, mostly magazines ("Temas," etc.). (Box 234)
- Materials related to Guatemala (newsletters, press releases, reports, etc.); publications, continued ("Temas," "La Republica," etc.). (Box 235)
- Newspapers ("El Tiempo Latino," etc.). (Box 236)
- Newspapers ("El Tiempo Latino," etc.); newsletters, reports, bulletins etc. mostly related to Guatemala; "Executive Intelligence Reviews" issues. (Box 237)
- "Executive Intelligence Reviews" issues, continued; "Agenda International, Inc." materials (releases, reports, etc.); bulletins, newsletters, etc. (including "Informador Guerrillero"). (Box 238)
- Bulletins, newsletters, miscellaneous publications (including "Informador Guerrillero," "!En Marcha!," "Food Monitor," "Defense and Foreign Affairs Weekly"). (Box 239)
- Bulletins, newsletters, miscellaneous publications, continued (including "Informador Guerrillero," "!En Marcha!," "Food Monitor," "Defense and Foreign Affairs Weekly"). (Box 240)
- Materials related to Nicaragua, 1989-1997 (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); miscellaneous. (Box 241)
- Materials related to Nicaragua and El Salvador; subject files arranged alphabetically, "C" (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 242)
- Materials related to Central America, especially Mexico; subject files arranged alphabetically, "C" and "E" (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 243)
- Materials related to Mexico (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 244)
- Materials related to Central America; other subject files arranged roughly in an alphabetical order, "Ce"-"Ci" (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 245)
- Materials related to Central America (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 246)
- Materials related to Mexico, Guatemala, El Salvador, Nicaragua [?]; subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 247)
- Materials related to Mexico and Argentina; subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 248)
- Materials related to Argentina, Bahamas, Haiti; subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 249)
- Materials related to Israel and Haiti; subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 250)
- Materials related to Argentina and Belize; subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 251)
- Materials related to Argentina and Haiti; subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 252)
- Materials related to Haiti, Bolivia, Chile; subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 253)
- Materials related to Bolivia (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); subject files ("Bush Administration," "Rainforests," etc.). (Box 254)
- Subject files - "Reagan Administration," etc. (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 255)
- Materials related to Canada; subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 256)
- Materials related to Suriname, Trinidad and Tobago, Puerto Rico, San Domingo; subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 257)
- Materials related to Puerto Rico; subject and personal files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 258)
- Materials related to Suriname and Puerto Rico (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); subject files ("Reagan - Latin America Policy," etc.). (Box 259)
- Materials related to Uruguay, mostly regarding human rights (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 260)
- Materials related to Suriname and Mexico; subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 261)
- Materials related to Mexico, Barbados, Belize, and Argentina; subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 262)
- Materials related to Argentina (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 263)
- Materials related to Mexico; subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 264)
- Materials related to Mexico and Argentina; subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 265)
- Materials related to Mexico and Argentina (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 266)
- Materials related to Mexico, Argentina, and Peru (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 267)
- Materials related to Peru (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 268)
- Materials related to Soviet Union, Peru, and Puerto Rico (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 269)
- Materials related to Puerto Rico (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 270)
- Materials related to Nicaragua; subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 271)
- Materials related to Nicaragua (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 272)
- Materials related to Nicaragua, Mexico; subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 273)
- Materials related to Nicaragua, Mexico, Argentina, Columbia; subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 274)
- Materials related to Argentina (mostly regarding Falklands problem and economy), Jamaica (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 275)
- Materials related to Mexico, Argentina, Martinique, Jamaica, Brazil, Guatemala (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.), miscellaneous. (Box 276)
- Materials related to Mexico and Argentina (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 277)
- Materials related to Mexico (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 278)
- Materials related to Argentina; subject and personal files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); miscellaneous. (Box 279)
- Miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 280)
- Miscellaneous subject files, continued (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 281)
- Materials related to El Salvador and Montenegro; subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 282)
- Materials related to El Salvador, mostly regarding military issues and land reform; miscellaneous (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 283)
- Materials related to El Salvador, mostly regarding land reform and human rights issues (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 284)
- Materials related to El Salvador (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.), miscellaneous. (Box 285)
- Miscellaneous subject files (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 286)
- Materials related to Nicaragua and Cuba (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 287)
- Materials related to Nicaragua and Costa Rica (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 288)
- Materials related to Nicaragua (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); miscellaneous subject files. (Box 289)
- Materials related to Cuba, Nicaragua, Costa Rica (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); subject files. (Box 290)
- Materials related to Nicaragua (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); subject files ("Debt," etc.). (Box 291)
- Materials related to Brazil, Canada (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); miscellaneous subject files ("Debt," "1986 Congress," etc.). (Box 292)
- Materials related to Antigua, Argentina, Belize, Barbados, Bolivia, Brazil, Chile, and Canada (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.). (Box 293)
- Materials related to Chile, Colombia, Cuba, Paraguay, and Peru (clippings, leaflets, publications, reports, correspondence, releases, etc.); miscellaneous. (Box 294)